Preliminary Guide to the Lisner Auditorium records, 1946-2005 RG0055
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Lisner Auditorium records
1946-2005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Lisner Auditorium
RG0055
125.75 Linear Feet
Materials in this collection include programs, posters, contracts, fiscal reports, correspondence, and photographs. They range in date from 1946 to 2005.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
The materials were transferred to the University Archives by the Director of the Lisner Auditorium.
Historical or Biographical Note
The George Washington University's Lisner Auditorium was named for Abram Lisner, University Trustee (1909-17, 1919-38), who bequeathed money in his will for its construction. Abram Lisner was a merchant, philanthropist, and University Trustee. The cornerstone was laid in 1941 and construction completed in 1943. The auditorium contains the mural of Augustus Vincent Tack. Lisner Auditorium was opened (for commercial use) in the fall of 1946 and for many years was the only sizeable facility of its kind in Washington. Mrs. Susan Whitney Dimock also bequeathed money for the Dimock Gallery, located next to the lower Lisner Lounge.
Lisner Auditorium is an important cultural resource for the city of Washington and offers a skillfully executed architectural achievement for the University campus. Designed by Waldron Faulkner of the architectural firm, Faulkner and Kingsbury, it was built by Charles H. Tompkins.
The auditorium is composed of marble with a spare, even extreme, design. While its inspiration is classical, the architects abstracted the design from the cube. The building stands as a geometric expression and contribution to period architecture. For many years it hosted GW's commencement exercises, and in the days before the Kennedy Center, it was the major focus of Washington. D.C. theater life.
The Director of Lisner reports to the Vice President for Information and Administration Services.
N.B. This history note was written in 2005
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include programs, posters, contracts, fiscal reports, correspondence, and photographs. They range in date from 1946 to 2005. Since it opened the auditorium has hosted many famous performing artists, including: Bill Monroe, Chick Corea, George Benson, Jay Leno, Joe Cocker, Mummenschanz, Pete Seeger, Supertramp, David Benoit, Twyla Tharp, Blues Traveler, Sheryl Crow, Branford Marsalis, The Knack, as well as local groups. The materials were transferred to the University Archives by the Director of the Lisner Auditorium.
Collection Organization
Organized into 57 series: Posters, Programs, Flyers, Pamphlets, Office Records, Photographs, Schedules, LP albums, Financial records, Contracts, Audio tapes.
Other materials note
Please note that MS2135 Series 7 Box 28 Folder 25 contains material related to the Lisner-Louise Dickson-Hurt Home and also the Will of Abraham Lisner.
Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Photographs; Washington (D.C.); Dimock Gallery; Performances; Lisner Auditorium; Audiotapes; Seeger, Pete; Supertramp (Musical group); Tharp, Twyla; Lisner, Abram; Marsalis, Branford; Monroe, Bill; George Washington University; Leno, Jay; Cocker, Joe; Mummenschanz (Group); Corea, Chick; Crow, Sheryl; Blues Traveler (Musical group); Dimock, Susan Whitney; Benoit, David; Benson, George; Knack (Musical group)
- Posters, 1967-1988; RG0055 Series 1; 8 Linear feet (Box 6, Box 7, Box 5, Box 3, Box 4, Box 2, Box 1, Box 8, Box 9)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of 546 performance posters from Lisner Auditorium. They range in date from 1967-88. The original numbering of the posters has been maintained.
  Formerly ACC#12; numbering of posters is continuous.
  - Betty - April 11, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Betty (autographed) - April 11, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Esta Noche Teatro - October 11, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Esta Noche Teatro - October 11, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Kujawaki performing troupe of Polish dancers, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Les Ballets Trockadero de Monte Carlo, 02/25/1977-02/27/1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Les Ballets Trockadero de Monte Carlo, 02/25/1977-02/27/1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Waiting on Godot, 05/03/1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Pan American Physique competition, 10/25/1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Roy Radin's Vaudeville Review, 12/05/1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Washington Ballet - Nutcracker, 12/13/1984-12/29/1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Firesign Theatre - May 12, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "The Right Stuff" movie poster, 10/18/1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Twelfth Night - December 14, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Iranian National Music - June 24, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Iranian National Music - June 24, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Joshua, 07/1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Xapie Aneeloy (Greek) - October 26, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Adrak-Ke-Panje (Hindi) - April 17, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The Romantics - October 15, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Yale Russian Chorus - April 1, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Merchant of Venice, 04/13-04/15 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Jeff Majors For Us All, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Holly Near and inti-illimani, 05/03/1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - As You Like It, 03/21/1969-03/22/1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Keith Pringle, 07/31/1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Le Tartuffe, 11/15/1968 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Le Tartuffe, 11/15/1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Julian Bream, 02/09/1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Julian Bream, 02/09/1969 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Lone Justice, 09/10/1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Tommy Makem & Liam Clancy in concert - March 14, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Arab American Club, 06/15/1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Travelin' Blues Workshop - September 18, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Hua Shing Goodwill Mission R.O.C., 07/26/1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Grupo Aymaro from Bolivia - September 27, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Haciendo Punto en Otio Son - Latin American New Song, 11/10/1981 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Tending the Dream (Ronnie Gilbert) - December 14, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Inward to the Sea, 11/06/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Peter Yarrow - April 23, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - "Copellia" Regional Ballet Company - June 18, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Pankaj Udhas, 04/06/1986 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Cloud Gate, Taipei Contemporary Dance Theatre, 11/04/1985-11/06/1985 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cloud Gate, Taipei Contemporary Dance Theatre, 11/04/1985-11/06/1985 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Gypsy Baron, 05/22/1982-05/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Ronnie Gilbert, 05/03/1985 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Ram Lila (India), 11/13/1987 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Weather Report - July 13, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Cleve Francis, 12/12/1986 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Hai Chia Variety Show, R.O.C., 03/24/1973-03/25/1973 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Inward to the Sea, meet Peter Benchley author of "Jaws", 09/20/1975 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Inward to the Sea, 09/20/1975 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Israel Folk Dance Festival, 04/04/1976 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Israel Folk Dance Festival, 03/16/1975 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Mercedes Sosa, 08/09/1986 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Tango Festival, 07/29/1932-07/30/1983 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Chick Corea and Gary Burton - February 10, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Chick Corea and Gary Burton - February 10, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Youth Goodwill Mission from R.O.C., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - John Fahey and insect Trust - May 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - John Ogdon - November 11, undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Music From Marlboro, 11/1967-04/1968 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Larry Groce - June 23, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Kuang Hua Goodwill Mission R.O.C., 10/12/1985 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Il Trovatore - November 23-25, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Norman Walker and Dance Company, 04/28/1969 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Norman Walker and Dance Company, 04/28/1969 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Prairie Home Companion - October 16-17, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Prairie Home Companion - October 16-17, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Higher Conscious - July 1-4, undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - National Ballet - April 4-6, undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Alicia deLarrocha, 11/18/1967 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Steve Forbert - October 20, undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Ram Dass - April 26-27, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Fotem Turkish Dance Ensemble, 04/10-04/11 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Margie Adam - April 7, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Washington For Jesus - April 29, undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Inward to the Sea, 11/05/1983 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Moliere, 11/09/1973 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Requiem for John F. Kennedy - February 18, undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Inward to the Sea, 11/01/1980 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, 01/26/1974 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, 06/16/1984 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Belushi Lives on - March 3, undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Tommy Makem and Liam Clancy, Farewell Tour, 03/1988 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Dona Francisquita - June 30, undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Kuban Cossacks, 04/10/1971 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Regional Ballet Company, 06/10/1973 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - G.W. Cherry Blossom Jazz Festival - April 8, undated (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Hebrew Academy of Greater Washington - Theodore Bikel - April 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Hebrew Academy of Greater Washington - Theodore Bikel - April 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Fairport Convention - May 18, undated (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - National Dance Theater of Zaire, 11/06/1981 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - National Dance Theater of Zaire, 11/06/1981 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Tribute to Marvin Gaye, 11/02/1985 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - The Bartered Bride - March 14-16, undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - The Chieftans - March 10, undated (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Todd Rundgren - October 24, undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Todd Rundgren - October 24, undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Captiol Ballet Company - November 21-22, undated (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Nuclear Winter changing our way of thinking, 04/18/1985 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Nuclear Winter changing our way of thinking, 04/18/1985 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Merce Cunningham and Dance Company, 02/20/1970-02/29/1979 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Grupo Cultural Amerindia & Centro de Arte, 07/15/1983 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Grupo Cultural Amerindia & Centro de Arte, 07/15/1983 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Twelfth Night - November 15-18, undated (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Twelfth Night - November 15-18, undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Firesign Theater: in Anytown USA - May 12, undated (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Free Campus Film Festival - December 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Kinky and the Texas Jewboys - November 15, undated (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Voodoo Masks Auction tonight, undated (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - David Oistraka (at Constitution Hall) - January 30-31, undated (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - David Oistraka (at Constitution Hall) - January 30-31, undated (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Good Woman of Setzuan, 11/11/1976-11/20/1976 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - John Fahey - May 5, undated (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Guiomar Novaes, 05/28/1968 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - New Riders of the Purple Sage - November 15, undated (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - New Riders of the Purple Sage - November 15, undated (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Ballet Spectacular - February 15-16, undated (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Ballet Spectacular - February 15-16, undated (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Antonio Janigroi, conductor, Chamber Orchestra of the SAAR - April 12, undated (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Music From Marlboro - January 25, undated (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Dimitris Squvros, 07/08/1984 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Doc Watson & Son, 02/09/1974 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Doc Watson & Son, 02/09/1974 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Billy Bragg - April 19, undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - National Lyric Opera, "Cavalleria Rusticana" - May 19, undated (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Yiannis Glezos, 06/22/1980 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Mummenschanz - February 14, undated (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Mummenschanz - February 14, undated (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Baltimore Symphony Orchestra - March 7, undated (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Fabulous Sabicas - King of Spanish guitar, 02/18/1967 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Fabulous Sabicas - King of Spanish guitar, 02/18/1967 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Outdoor Sculpture of D.C. lecture, 09/30/1974 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Johann Sebastian Bach International competition - May 25-26, undated (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Johann Sebastian Bach International competition - May 25-26, undated (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Israeli Variety Show - March 30, undated (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Festival of the Nations - May 10-19, undated (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Japan Festival, 04/03/1987-04/17/1987 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - City Dance, 04/29/1981-05/01/1981 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Alarm Strength - May 13, undated (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Antranig Armenian Dance ensemble, 05/30/1981 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - The Knack - October 9, undated (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Calypso Fiesta with Mighty Sparrow, 05/19/1984 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Lord Brynner, Calypso Reggey King, 10/16/1973 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Lord Brynner, Calypso Reggey King, 10/16/1973 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - James Dillet Freeman - November 11, undated (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Kate Clinton - May 5, undated (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Maryland Ballet, 03/31/1979 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Martha Graham - October 11, undated (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Kundirana (music ministry), 05/06/1986 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Misa Criolla (Argentine folk mass), 10/20/1971 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Misa Criolla (Argentine folk mass), 10/20/1971 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Jagjit and Chitra Singh - May 29, undated (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Joshua Rifkin - November 17, undated (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Joshua Rifkin - November 17, undated (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Michael Hedges & Liz Story - October 4, undated (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 04/13/1972-04/15/1972 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 04/13/1972-04/15/1972 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 04/13/1972-04/15/1972 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Romen Gypsy Theatre - October 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Franco and his T.P.O.K. Jazz from Zaire, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Franco and his T.P.O.K. Jazz from Zaire, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Ding Mercado, 05/25/1985 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Supertramp, 06/16/1977 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - London Savoyards, 01/13/1979-01/14/1979 (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Tommy Makem & Liam Clancy (autographed by Clancy), undated (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Washington Ballet, undated (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Mr. North America and Jr. Mr. America, 06/20/1981 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - J.S. Bach International Competitions - June 15-17, undated (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Hampton Jazz Festival, 06/27/1968-06/28/1968 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Second Artificial Intellegence Satellite symposium, 06/25/1986 (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Non-Stop Britain '72, 11/02/1972-11/03/1972 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Antrang Armenian Dance ensemble, 06/10/1978 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Chick Correa Elekric Band - October 22, undated (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Awaji Puppet Theatre of Japan - February 10, undated (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Awaji Puppet Theatre of Japan - February 10, undated (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Mahmud Mirza (sitar music), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Capital Ballet Company - November 16-17, undated (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Capital Ballet Company - November 16-17, undated (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Twyla Tharp, 02/12/1976-02/13/1976 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Twyla Tharp, 02/12/1976-02/13/1976 (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Mariza Koch, 06/22/1980 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - Livingston Taylor - November 16, undated (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Livingston Taylor - November 16, undated (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - WMATA (Metro) Annual Employee Awards Ceremony, 06/10/1987 (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - A Match Made in Heaven (Yiddish musical comedy) - March 2, undated (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - Compagnie Nationale De Danses Francaises (at Constitution Hall), 01/27/1968 (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Best of Broadway, 03/09/1969 (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Best of Broadway, 03/09/1969 (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Karmapa of Tibet, 09/23/1980 (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Karmapa of Tibet, 09/23/1980 (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Annual Student Christmas Show and Sale - November 8-December 7, undated (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Clancy Brothers, 11/04/1972 (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Calypso Socafest, 08/24/1985 (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Kinhmatooeatpo (Greek troupe), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Kinhmatooeatpo (Greek troupe), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - Uri Geller - November 7, undated (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Uri Geller - November 7, undated (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Fabulous Clancy Brothers, 03/06/1982 (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Fabulous Clancy Brothers, 03/06/1982 (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - Tommy Makem & Liam Clancy - March 16, undated (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - Les Ballets Jazz - March 2-4, undated (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - inti-illimani - March 15, undated (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - Army Soldiers Show "We the People", 11/21/1986-11/22/1986 (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - Washington Ballet - The Nutcracker, 12/13/1984-12/29/1984 (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - Washington Ballet - The Nutcracker, 12/13/1984-12/29/1984 (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Oro in concert, 06/22/1985 (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - Jose Limon Dance Company, 02/08/1974 (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Jose Limon Dance Company, 02/08/1974 (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - Inward to the Sea, 11/07/1981 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - Performing Arts Company of the People's Republic of China, 10/10/1984-10/13/1984 (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - Hansel and Gretel, 01/18-01/20 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - Rock Against Apartheid - May 9, undated (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - Modern Dance Series - July 14-August 11, undated (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater, 03/05/1970 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater, 03/05/1970 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - Quilapayun (Chilean musical group), 05/14/1986 (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Disney Auditions, 01/31/1987 (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Daniel Shafran, 02/28/1977 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, 11/21/1982 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - Caligula Camus, 11/30/1970 (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - Fu Hsing Chinese Opera, 03/17/1985 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Fu Hsing Chinese Opera, 03/17/1985 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - Tommy Makem & Liam Clancy - March 10, undated (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - George Faison, 12/05/1975-12/06/1975 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Ballet Spectacular - March 13, undated (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Ballet Spectacular - March 13, undated (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - Block Party with Nighthawks, 04/10/1976 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Mighty Sparrow, Winston Sosa, Sam and the Caribbean Express, 05/01/1988 (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - Dimitri, 11/12/1976 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - Dimitri - October 24, undated (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Bonnie Raitt (at Constitution Hall) - August 17, undated (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Salvation Army, 05/17/1985-05/19/1985 (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Lucho Munoz, 05/29/1988 (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - Ionesco's, 02/20/1974 (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Argentina in Concert - October 10, undated (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Look Homeward, Angel, 03/11/1966-03/12/1966 (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - The King Meets the Grand Master, 05/24/1987 (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - Capella Russian chorus, 09/20/1980 (Box 4, Folder 241)
  - John Williams, 04/13/1969 (Box 4, Folder 242)
  - Evening of Jazz Tap Dancing - October 7-9, undated (Box 4, Folder 243)
  - Cleve, undated (Box 4, Folder 244)
  - Calypso Extravaganza with Mighty Sparrow, 05/14/1983 (Box 4, Folder 245)
  - Bryan Bowers and Seldon Scene, 03/23/1974 (Box 4, Folder 246)
  - Bryan Bowers and Seldon Scene, 03/23/1974 (Box 4, Folder 247)
  - Bobcat Goldthwait, 06/23/1988 (Box 4, Folder 248)
  - Holly Near and Flirtations - November 11, undated (Box 4, Folder 249)
  - The Little Humpbacked Horse, 04/21/1979-04/28/1979 (Box 4, Folder 250)
  - Simon Wiesenthal - March 29, undated (Box 4, Folder 251)
  - Simon Wiesenthal - March 29, undated (Box 4, Folder 252)
  - Hermanos Ayala, 11/16/1984 (Box 4, Folder 253)
  - National Ballet - April 5-24, undated (Box 4, Folder 254)
  - Washington Ballet, 03/13/1978-03/21/1978 (Box 4, Folder 255)
  - WMATA (Metro): Annual Employee Awards Ceremony, 06/22/1988 (Box 4, Folder 256)
  - Welcome to the Go-Go featuring Trouble Funk, 07/12/1984 (Box 4, Folder 257)
  - Bonnie Raitt (at Smith Center), 04/09/1978 (Box 4, Folder 258)
  - Doodling (a play), 07/12/1980 (Box 4, Folder 259)
  - If I Should Die - February 22, undated (Box 4, Folder 260)
  - Andre Kole World of Illusion, 10/14/1983 (Box 4, Folder 261)
  - Bluegrass Benefit - January 20, undated (Box 4, Folder 262)
  - Cambodian Dance and Music, 12/12/1981 (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - MISR International "Alexandre..Pourquoi?", undated (Box 4, Folder 264)
  - Union Café by Jehane Dyllan, undated (Box 4, Folder 265)
  - God's love is eternal and Everlasting - St. Teresa Gospel Choir - January 26, undated (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - Ariana Muska - Live!, video production, undated (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - Ariana Muska - Live!, video production, undated (Box 4, Folder 268)
  - Bat Dor Israel Dance Company - February 27-March 1, undated (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - Caribbean Extravaganza, 05/15/1982 (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - Charles Aznavour, 11/10/1973 (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - Charles Aznavour, 11/10/1973 (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - The Tabernacle Echoes, 04/27/1980 (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - Ana Martinez, 04/28/1985 (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - Ana Martinez, 04/28/1985 (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - U.S. Marine Band Concert Series, 03/02/1980-04/27/1980 (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - Francescatti, 01/18/1968 (Box 4, Folder 277)
  - Francescatti, 01/18/1968 (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - Harolyn Blackwell (autographed), 04/26/1987 (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - Harolyn Blackwell, 04/26/1987 (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - Pete Seeger & Sechaba Singers - September 10, undated (Box 4, Folder 281)
  - Casa Cuba, 05/20/1973 (Box 4, Folder 282)
  - National Chinese Opera Theatre - October 18, undated (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - Oratorio Society of Montgomery County, 11/17/1968 (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - Hot Tuna in Concert, 09/25/1974 (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - Grass of 80 reunion concert featuring the Seldom Scene - February 17, undated (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - Symphony of Psalms, 04/17/1988 (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - Paddy Noonan Irish Show - March 30, undated (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - Casselberry-Dupree & Cris Williamson - October 9, undated (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - Rev. Sun Myung Moon - October 21-23, undated (Box 4, Folder 290)
  - Country Gentlemen andSeldom Scene, 10/14/1972 (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - Faust, 12/10/1982-12/11/1982 (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - Computer Music Concert - June 30, undated (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - Lucinda Childs Dance Company, 10/29/1981-10/30/1981 (Box 4, Folder 294)
  - Muscular Dystrophy Benefit concert with Nighthawks, 03/31/1981 (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - Horatio Cuarany - May 28, undated (Box 4, Folder 296)
  - Kun Woo Paik Piano, undated (Box 4, Folder 297)
  - Miss Black America D.C. Pageant, 06/13/1981 (Box 4, Folder 298)
  - College Girl of the Year, 04/02/1974-04/05/1974 (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - Ali Akbar Khan - February 8, undated (Box 4, Folder 300)
  - Ali Akbar Khan - February 8, undated (Box 4, Folder 301)
  - John Williams - November 7, undated (Box 4, Folder 302)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company - January 27-29, undated (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - Ding Mercado, 03/09/1986 (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - Traditional Irish Musicians, 10/22/1973 (Box 4, Folder 305)
  - Discover New Zealand, 03/22/1986 (Box 4, Folder 306)
  - Mummenschanz, 02/05/1977 (Box 4, Folder 307)
  - Mummenschanz, 02/05/1977 (Box 4, Folder 308)